I don't remember much about them.
So you know.
But do you know what?
We start, we start a couple of books.
Start with the one I liked at least and ends with the one I liked best.
The first books I want to talk about are actually three books.
Because I think I merges them here in some way.
And it is actually "dust off", a couple of books that I have had for any length of time.
Very long.
And I have grazed these three books in a series.
It's 6-7-8, numbers 6-7-8.
And I have grazed them.
Botswana's first female detective.
And MMA Ramotswe, I think she pronounces it.
And she solves cases.
This is a cozy deck deluxe.
And I think I've read some cozy books nowadays.
And I feel that now I'm up here with them.
I feel now.
For several reasons.
This series is really a cozy deck.
Where the cases must not take place so much.
Without it, it is more about those who work with her.
Now I have to talk about a book that helped my TBR.
As all other books had to wait.
I jumped on the train at once.
I'll be honest.
This is a book that the whole world has been waiting for.
At least I waited extremely impatient was me.
But when I got it, I swallowed it pretty much.
But, there is a men.
I talked about Atlas.
What is it called?
The story of Pa Salt by Lucinda Riley.
Who and what and how.
In this book.
It delivers absolutely.
At the same time, I'm a little disappointed.
Because it is still a brick.
Shall we see.
Over 600 pages.
So it's very tall, it's a brick
Despite that, I feel and I feel that it is accelerated.
It goes so fast.
Such pink shimmer around this.
How hard times they go through.
Pa salt goes through.
Who has killed the dog?
This starts with some sort of
We are inside his head.
Here one begins
a little of one
mystery as he solves
leading him to
things within their own family
which is revolving to him.
I gave it a four I think.
Three and a half, three and seventy five maybe.